{
    "id": "ayumihirono",
    "name": "廣野鮎美",
    "yomi": "Ayumi Hirono",
    "text": [
        "Hello. A curtain in my room is green, my favourite stuffed animal is yellow, a coat I recently bought is black.",
        "こんにちは。部屋のカーテンは緑、お気に入りのぬいぐるみは黄色、最近買ったコートは黒です。"
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Website",
            "href": "https://15hirono.wixsite.com/hironoayumi/"
        },
        {
            "a": "Twitter",
            "href": "https://www.twitter.com/HIRONO_Ayumi_/"
        },
        {
            "a": "Instagram",
            "href": "https://www.instagram.com/10rikera___/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Let's eat Gyoza! Because",
            "jp": "餃子食べよ",
            "yes": "it's sunny today.",
            "left": "晴れてるから",
            "no": "my stomach tells me so.",
            "right": "胃がそう言ってるから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Let's go to the park. Because",
            "jp": "公園行こ",
            "yes": "I want to walk",
            "left": "歩きたいから",
            "no": "I want to talk",
            "right": "話したいから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Let's watch the rising sun! Because",
            "jp": "朝日見よ",
            "yes": "I saw it on the TV yesterday.",
            "left": "昨日テレビで見たから",
            "no": "I am in the mountain now.",
            "right": "今山にいるから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Let's go to the book store. Because",
            "jp": "本屋行こ",
            "yes": "I found it.",
            "left": "見つけたから",
            "no": "it was on the road.",
            "right": "落ちてたから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "Let's talk! Because",
            "jp": "話そ",
            "yes": "my hair has grown.",
            "left": "髪が伸びたから",
            "no": "I saw a UFO.",
            "right": "UFO見たから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Let's dig potatoes! Because",
            "jp": "じゃがいも掘ろ",
            "yes": "I haven't ever seen a shooting star.",
            "left": "流れ星見たことないしさ",
            "no": "I want to go to Germany.",
            "right": "ドイツ行きたいし"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Chocolate. Because",
            "jp": "チョコレート",
            "yes": "it's cold.",
            "left": "寒いから",
            "no": "the parcel isn't delivered yet.",
            "right": "宅配便が届かないから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Let's go out together. Because",
            "jp": "デートしましょう",
            "yes": "the wind brew.",
            "left": "風が吹いたから",
            "no": "I like green.",
            "right": "緑が好きだから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "I am at the top of the building. Because",
            "jp": "ビルのてっぺん",
            "yes": "I want to see the sky.",
            "left": "空が見たいから",
            "no": "I want to see the clouds.",
            "right": "雲が見たいから"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "A excuse",
            "jp": "口実",
            "yes": "I need some.",
            "left": "いる",
            "no": "I don't need it.",
            "right": "いらない"
        }
    ]
}